RESUME

Lakhan Singh

Mobile: +91-797-417-8134

Email: <u>lakhanchauhan105@gmail.com</u>
Address: 805 Royale Tower, Etawah (U.P.)

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY:-

I am having 3+ year of experience as an civil site Engineering deals with the design, construction ,maintenance and modernization of "New retail outlet" including work like building construction, billing, calculating "Bar bending schedule" maintaining "Daily progress report", managing manpower, materials and tools requirement in site . I would also like to utilise my skills to finish the project as per given time, handling client, having good communication skills ,being responsible,self-motivated and creating a positive attitude in a good work environment.

WORK EXPERIENCE:-

SITE ENGINEER:- Vaishno construction [2017-2021]

- Manage and co-ordinate all site activities to ensure smooth project implementation as per drawing under quality and standard .
- Continuously monitoring multiple project to ensure all work done as per given time period.
- Calculating bar bending schedule, maintaining Daily progress report and do billing .
- Report to the project manager on the daily progress of works, resource utilisation and manpower status.
- Attend department meetings to view cost incurred to date.
- Handling client, manpower, materials and tools requirement and work progress in site.

QUALITY AND SAFETY ENGINEER:- Quality Austria Central Asia [2021-Till Date]

- Developing plan, procedure and design systems to prevent staff from getting hurt/injured and also keep the property from getting damage.
- Execute plans, design and specification for construction of new retail outlets.
- Managing man-power and co-operate with client for material purchasing.
- Perform all aspects of onsite accident investigations for entire project.
- Cost estimation and budgeting.

EDUCATION:-

2013 - 2017	Lakshmi Inst. Of Tech., RGPV UniversityCivil engineering	Bhopal, MP	(IND)
2012-2013	Sarvodaya Inter College • Science	Uttar Pradesh	(IND)
2011	Gyansthali Academy, C.B.S.E • Science	Uttar Pradesh	(IND)

EDUCATION & INTERNSHIP SUMMARY:-

B.Tech Project:-

Project name: Self compacting concrete.

• **Project description**: Preparing and perform SCC on a Beam.

Project duration: Summer training of 4 weeks at central public department.
 Project Findings: Provide superior strength, durability, and fast placement without vibration and mechanical consolidations so it need less energy and reduced

skilled labor, Economy and Time saving.

SKILL's:-

- Billing.
- Bar bending schedule.
- Project management.
- Maintain Daily progress report.
- Managing manpower and client.
- Good communication skill.

EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES:-

- Playing cricket.
- Swimming

STRENGTHS

- Friendliness.
- Motivational skill.
- Self believe and self-confidence.
- Work in a team with great enthusiasm.

PERSONAL DETAILS:-

Date of birth: 26th march 1994

Nationality : India Sex : Male

Interested In: Reading books, creative drawing and social work.

Languages known. : Hindi, English, Kannada